姑娘们 我需要你们听我说件事
Girls, I need your attention.
在大多数的地方 你还需要儿童垫高椅呢
You also need a booster seat for most places.
不是 我出来是要跟你们说件大事
No, I came out to tell you some big news.
你穿这毛衣来上班时
You also came out
也从出来变成出柜了
when you wore that sweater to work today.
约翰·梅尔拍时尚杂志的同款好吗
John Mayer wore this sweater in Details.
今晚 我们要试试家庭式服务
Tonight, we are trying family-style service.
我还以为家庭式服务
I thought family-style service was
是指我叔叔让我"做"的那些事呢
what I had to do with my uncle.
我家庭的风格是"百乐餐"
Well, my family-style is more "potluck"--
百倍大麻
heavy on the pot,
乐子砍半
not so heavy on the luck.
为什么会有家庭来这里
Why would a family come here?
如果我看到有小孩进来 我会打给警察叔叔
If I see a child in here, I'm calling the police.
就像大热天看到有狗被锁在车里一样
It's like seeing a dog locked in a hot car.
猎人烤鸡 家庭风
Chicken cacciatore , family-style.
洋葱炒肝 家庭风
Liver and onions, family-style.
肉丸意面 我的家庭风
Spaghetti and meatballs, my family-style,
也就是"肉丸"有点小
which means the balls are kinda small,
但是"意面"绝对是"加长版"
but the noodles are extra long.
你们把装有食物的大盆子端出去
You bring out the food in large bowls
客人可以自助取餐
and the customers serve themselves,
反正我雇了你们俩后 顾客基本靠自助
as they've been doing since I hired you two.
好主意啊 阿憨
Good idea, Han.
餐厅的食物的确适合放大盆子里
The diner food does belong in a big bowl--
放屎盆子里
the toilet bowl.
我真不知道你叔叔是看上你哪点
I don't know what your uncle saw in you.
麦克斯 我在手机上发现非常糟心的东西
Max, I just found something very upsetting on my phone.
苹果又硬要送U2乐团的专辑了吗
Another free U2 album?
更惨
Worse.
比受邀请去看朋友的即兴剧团演出还惨
And worse than an e-vite to a friend's improv show.
我收到一封电邮
It's an e-mail from the managing director
是管理"嗨翻天"所有门店的总经理发的
of all The High restaurants saying he's seen our sales
他说对我们的业绩与表现很不满
and is disappointed with my performance.
切 删了
Duh-lete...
那些男人在炮后发给我的"不满意"短信
like I do with all the "disappointed in your performance" texts
我也都是直接删掉啊
I get from guys after sex.
男士们 抱歉
Sorry, gents!
我的胸器许下了
My boobs makes a promise
我的弱背做不到的承诺
my bad back can't deliver.
业绩难看不是我们的错
Those bad sales numbers are not our fault.
我们的店在机场角落
Our unit's out at the airport.
那是你的店
Well, I'm not taking ownership of this
因为我的那根"电"不在机场
because my unit is not at the airport.
而是在我的床头柜里
It's in my bed table drawer.
我是经理 责任在我
I'm the manager. It's on me.
就像这调味酱渍 在我身衣服上这死不出来
As is this tartar stain. It just refuses to come out.
死不出来[柜]的程度 像它爸妈是浸信会的
You'd think it's parents were Baptist.
经理大人 我明天得早退
Well, Manager, I need to get out of there
我得去做苏菲的婚礼蛋糕
early tomorrow to do Sophie's wedding cake,
还因为你是个讨人厌的老板
and also because you're annoying as a boss.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
我 我 我 我 我
Me, me, me, me, me,
我 我 我 我
me, me, me, me...
我好爱当新娘的这段时间
I love being a bride.
因为我都不用假装我在乎别人的事
You don't even have to pretend it's about anyone else.
跟我有点像 我有钱那会也这样
Kinda like me, when I was rich.
现在的你每天也还是如此啊
Pretty much every single day still.
有好消息 也有坏消息
Good news, bad news.
好消息是皮疹到我的蛋蛋就没再扩散
The good news is the rash is not spreading past my nuts.
而这还是他的好消息
And that's the good news.
坏消息是 我们预定好的
Bad news-- the wedding donkey we booked
在教堂婚礼出现的驴子死掉了
for the church service died.
我来问一个明摆着的问题
I'll ask the obvious question.
它是因为被"传染"皮疹而死吗
Did it have anything to do with the rash?
那我们该怎么办
I mean, what are we gonna do?
如果没有一头傻驴走红毯
It's not a traditional Polish wedding
就算不上是传统波兰式婚礼了
without an ass walking down the aisle.
"傻驴走红毯"的这事奥列格承包了
I think Oleg's got that covered.
姑娘们 我们需要头驴子 你们有匹马
Girls, we need an ass, you have a horse--
同科[家] 但没血缘关系
same family, but not related,
就像朱莉-皮特家的那帮孩子
like the Jolie-Pitt kids.
不行 栗宝是我的宝贝
No way. Chestnut is my baby.
那头驴子本来有一千块钱酬劳呢
Well, the donkey was getting a thousand bucks.
宝贝得工作啦
Baby's gotta work.
来客人的速度比第三季的
Wow, business is slower than the third season
《纸牌屋》的进度还慢
of House of Cards.
但你知道谁那里很来人吗
You know what's doing great business?
我的基佬约炮软件个人主页
It's my new Grindr profile.
把我的账户名改成了"高速真空吸引鸡"
Changed my screen name to "Suction Junction".
隔壁的"肉桂卷"面包店抢了我们所有生意
That damn Cinnabon next door is taking all our business.
没见识的人才会宁愿吃那些
What kind of low lives would prefer those
也不来吃我们的高档甜点呢
to these fine desserts?
我找到了去肉桂卷后厨的秘密通道
I found a secret pathway to the Cinnabon kitchen!
贱货 闪开
Move, bitch!
不是吧 你也沦陷了
Really? You too?
我实在是不懂啊
I just don't get it.
尝过才会懂 就像冰毒一样
It's an acquired taste, like crystal meth.
太棒了 我请的服务员又要迟到了
Great. My waiter's gonna be late again.
"被运输安全局拦下来了"
"Held up at the TSA line."
请一个叫默罕默德·马赫丁吉哈德的人
That's what I get for hiring an airport waiter
来当机场服务员 我真是自找麻烦
named Mohammed Machdinajihad.
看 洛妮 新店呢
Oh, look, Ronnie, a new place.
我看到了 波妮 我就在你旁边
I see it, Bonnie, I'm right next to you.
这里不是以前我们上机前
Didn't this used to be the bar we got wasted in
喝得烂醉的酒吧吗
before our flights?
我记不得 当时太醉了
I can't remember. I was wasted.
欢迎来到嗨翻天
Welcome to The High--
赞到翻天的高品质甜点
the finest in high quality desserts.
我们也有酸奶 卡布奇诺 拿铁 咖啡
We also have yogurts, cappuccinos, lattes, coffee,
花草茶与高档矿泉水
herb teas, or smart waters.
我告诉你们本店还有付费无线网热点了吗
And did I mention we're a Boingo Hotspot?
收敛点好吗
Take it down a notch.
你硬要讨人喜欢的程度
You're selling it harder than Anne Hathaway
比安妮·海瑟薇上《今夜秀》时还夸张
on The Tonight Show.
你们好 我不是来买的 我就看看
Oh, hi, I'm not here to buy, just to look.
我在减肥
On a diet...
从1998年就开始减了
since 1998.
天啊 它们看起来好赞
Oh dear lord, those look amazing.
-我能闻一下吗 -波妮 别
- Can I just smell a piece? - Bonnie, don't.
那会唤醒你的馋虫 我们飞到巴黎的途中
It'll get you going, and then halfway to Paris,
我又会抓到你躲在经济舱狂吃薯片
I'll find you in coach binging on a bag of Sun Chips.
这是我的工作里我最喜欢的一部分
That's my favorite thing about the job.
说到巴黎我就想到
Oh, Paris reminds me.
我买了两张去巴黎的头等舱机票
I bought two first class tickets to Paris--
刷三张信用卡 分期六年 多还20%的钱
on three credit cards that will escalate 20% over six years--
反正就是
anyway...
我真的需要把这票给退了
I really need to return them.
你们航空公司的退款期限是多久
What's the window on that with your airline?
一个月 大概跟我脸上这假笑
A month--about the same amount of time I have
终于笑不出来的时间差不多长
until this fake smile finally falls off my face.
妹子 我们是空姐
Lady, we're flight attendants.
如果你脸上那笑容没了
If that smile falls off your face,
那你估计就得去西南航空找工作了
you're gonna have to get a job at Southwest.
为什么要退货啊 你不喜欢巴黎吗
Why are you returning them? You don't like Paris?
爱死巴黎了 但要长话短说嘛...
J'adore Paris, but long story short--
我来帮你吧 因为她从来不懂短说
Uh, I'll make it short because she's incapable
而且还会多说一大堆假法语
and will throw in lots more of that fake French.
我们买票是为了去见一个
Bought the tickets so that I could get to the gate
当时的炮友小帅哥
to see a guy I was banging.
我懂你
I hear ya.
我有一次躲在行李车里12个小时
I once hid in the luggage cart for 12 hours
就为了去见一个在海关工作的男的
to do it with this cute guy who works at customs here.
对 叫瑞克 他最近在干嘛
Oh, right. Rick. What's he doing now?
干我 每隔三周的周二开干
Me, every third Tuesday.
姐妹们跟我也来击个掌
Ahh, don't leave me hanging, ladies.
要不是我们才在酒会读完《向前一步》
Ah. If we hadn't just read Lean In in our wine club--
我是说读书会
I mean book club--
我们一定会超嫉妒你们俩
We'd be real jealous of you gals.
我们一直梦想要在机场开家店
We always had a dream to open a shop at the airport.
无论你们想开什么 千万别开在肉桂卷隔壁
Well, whatever it is, just don't open near a Cinnabon
因为你的失败会有一股浓浓的肉桂味
because failure smells a hell of a lot like cinnamon.
前往巴黎的24号航班最后登机宣布
Final boarding call for flight 24 to Paris.
最后登机广播
Final boarding call.
最后登机广播了呀 那我们得快点啊
Final boarding call? We better hurry.
这里的一切突然看起来
Wow, everything looks so much smaller in here
比我印象中小啊
than I remembered it.
就像是回到当年高中母校
Like returning to your old high school...
或者是回想当年男朋友的小鸡鸡
or your old high school boyfriend's penis.
我的不是 我去的可是城里的高中
Not mine. I went to an urban high school.
怎么有股奇怪的味道
What's that weird smell?
大概是那罐牛奶吧 在这里太久了
Probably that milk. It's been in here so long,
瓶子上的照片是都变它自己了
its own photo was on the carton.
是在这里 好刺鼻的一股味儿
No, it's over here. Really pungent.
太棒了
Yes!
我可能欠了你们两位一点房租
Mm-- I might owe you two some rent.
除非你们愿意收大麻抵债
Unless you wanna settle in weed.
我一直都很乐意收大麻抵债[定居]
I always wanna settle in weed.
其实我还计划在那里退休
In fact, I plan to retire there.
柜里藏大麻
Marijuana's in the closet?
这比梅勒迪斯·巴克斯特出柜还让人吃惊
This is more shocking than Meredith Baxter-Birney.
我想既然你们俩不要这小蛋糕店了
Look, I figured since you two abandoned the cupcake shop,
这地方不用也是浪费
this space was available.
而且打从我70岁过后
Also, I stopped asking permission for stuff
我就不再征求别人许可了
when I turned 70.
我们没有不要这里好吗
We did not abandon it.
我们只是没怎么理它三个月了而已
We just haven't paid attention to it in 3 months,
就像我对我大腿中段以上的毛发一样
like me with any hair above my mid-thigh.
还说呢
Tell me about it.
你穿着那裙子弯腰的时候
When you bend over in that skirt,
我还以为你要生出爆炸头男星了
it looks like you're giving birth to Art Garfunkel.
我 我 我 我 我 我 我
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me!
太好了 厄尔 你在这
Oh, good. Earl, you're here.
是的 请不要跟我任何一位前妻说
Yes, I am. Don't tell any of my ex-wives.
厄尔 我有荣幸邀请你
Earl, would you do me the honor
明晚婚礼上牵着我走红毯吗
and walk me down the aisle tomorrow night?
苏菲 抱歉
Sophie, sorry.
我不知道你的父亲已经去世了
I didn't know your father was dead.
他是在见奥列格时死的吗
Did he die upon meeting Oleg?
他没死啦
Oh, he's not dead,
但我可不想被一个铁肺给抢走众人目光
but I'm not getting upstaged by an iron lung.
厄尔 你怎么忍心拒绝
Well, Earl, how could you say no
这么"诚心"的邀请呢
to such a heartfelt request?
苏菲 能牵你走是我莫大荣幸
I'd be honored, Sophie.
就像婚礼常说到的
Like the wedding saying goes,
旧的东西 新的东西
Something old, something new,
借的东西
something borrowed,
与黑色人类
and someone black.
卡洛琳 看
Oh, Caroline, look.
这是给栗宝戴的粉色缎带
Here are the pink ribbons for Chestnut.
栗宝身上非得系这么女生的缎带吗
Chestnut has to be covered in girly ribbons?
我怎么能这么对我的儿子
I can't do that to my boy.
我再加50块
I'll throw in another 50.
我想"马"子跟婊子这么音似
I guess there's a reason "horse" sounds
是有原因的
so much like "whore."
我们明晚6点出发去教堂
Now, we're all gonna leave for the church at 6:00,
但我跟厄尔说了4点
but I told Earl 4:00,
原因...我想你也懂
'cause, well... you know.
你这是怎么回事
What's happening over there?
麦克斯 你在哼歌
Max, you're humming!
什么
What?
别闹了
Please...
我才不哼歌[悍马]呢
I am not a hummer.
我只可能开着悍马
I mean, I'll drive in them,
帮人哼哼口交 但绝对不会哼歌
I'll give them, but I am not one.
天啊 我真的在哼歌 我是哪里有问题
Oh, my God, I am humming! What's wrong with me?
接下来我还会怎么样 微笑吗
What am I gonna do next, smile?
没错 今天的特别促销活动
That's right! Today's special promotion,
进店到出店只需五分钟
in and out in five minutes
超时甜品一律半价
or your dessert is half off.
吃屎吧 肉桂卷
Eat it, Cinnabon.
梨子果馅饼与咖啡
Pear tart and a coffee.
速度点啊 我这时间紧迫
Come on, I'm on a clock here.
他妈谁的梨子果馅饼与咖啡
Who had the damn pear tart and a coffee?
麦克斯 快点 五分钟进出
Max, hurry! Five minutes, in and out!
这世上唯一一件不需要你来教我的事
Yeah, the one thing you don't have to explain
就是"进与出"
to me is "in and out."
我需要帮忙 我从没说过我快
I need help! I never said I was fast.
我所有的高中辅导员都很"快"
All my high school guidance counselors did,
但我可没有
but I did not.
我去让强哥结束休息时间
I'll go get John off break
因为我们的服务员还是没到
because my waiter still isn't here.
这整个与中东的紧张关系
This whole Middle East situation
真是给我造成大大的不便
is just so inconvenient for me.
好的 现在我们有个真的大问题了
Okay, now we have a real situation.
你打人了 靠 麦克斯
You hit someone. Damn it, Max.
跟我无关 是苏菲
It's not about me. It's Sophie.
她的婚纱从波兰寄到了
Her gown arrived from Poland
现在被卡在外面海关那里
and it's stuck in customs out here.
我的婚纱
My gown!
我漂漂的婚纱
My beautiful gown!
天啊 我的婚纱
Oh, my God! My gown!
看来她很不开心啊
Wow. She is really upset.
是非常不开心
Really upset,
没按免提都已经这音量了
'cause this isn't even on speaker.
的确很棘手 但往好的一面看
Yes, it's awful, but look on the bright side.
我们绝对丑死人不偿命的伴娘服
Our certain-to-be-hideous bridesmaids dresses
也被卡在海关了
are stuck in customs too.
没 伴娘服过关了
No, those arrived.
靠 先有中东问题
Damn it! First, it's the Middle East,
然后伴娘服又来了
now those dresses.
我真是一刻都不能休息啊
I cannot catch a break.
哇 这里人好满啊
Wow, this place is packed.
还记得我们吗 波妮与洛妮
Remember us? Bonnie and Ronnie?
我们之前认识的
We knew you when.
等等 洛妮
Hey, wait, uh, Ronnie,
你上次不是说你在跟一个海关人员搞吗
didn't you say that you boned a guy in customs?
是波妮 我是有节操的人
That was Bonnie. I have standards...
而且他不喜欢我
and he didn't like me.
我解释一下 我的确是有跟海关人员上床
To be clear, I did have sex with the customs guy,
但不是在海关里搞
but not in customs.
我们是在家庭厕所里开搞
It was in one of those family bathrooms.
你有任何方法能够帮我们
Look, is there any way you could help us
从海关那里弄出一个包裹吗
get a package out of customs?
等等 我今天穿哪件胸罩
Wait... What bra am I wearing?
没问题
Oh, done!
强哥 我们有事先走 这里交给你了
John, we're leaving. You're in charge.
麦克斯 我们不能现在走啊
Max! We can't leave right now.
婚礼是今晚才开始 而我们正在
The wedding's not till tonight and we're in the middle
店铺促销活动中 而且要输了
of a store promotion and we're losing.
你知道我会宰了你对吧
You know I'm gonna kill you, right?
等我想好怎么宰就动手
I just have to figure out how.
目前最有可能的是把你的项链
Top contender is hooking your necklace
勾到前门上 然后让门往上升
on the front gate and pushing up.
我们能留多久是多久
We'll stay as late as possible.
到时候再去领苏菲的婚纱盒然后跳上地铁
Just pick up Sophie's dress box and hop on the subway.
轻轻松松
Easy peasy.
请注意 列车车门即将关闭
Watch the closing doors, please.
为什么任何事都不是轻轻松松
Why is nothing easy peasy?
请注意 列车车门即将关闭
Watch the closing doors, please.
我很注意了好吗
I am watching the doors!
很难不注意 车门都要吃了我箱子了
It's hard not to. They're about to eat my box.
哈哈哈 好好笑
Yeah, real funny, sir.
有妞说"吃我箱子[阴户]" 幼稚鬼
A girl said, "eat my box." grow up.
天啊 婚纱怎么能这么大件呢
Jeez! How could a dress be this big?
这还只是头纱
This is just the veil.
我得从包包里拿点东西出来
I have to get something out of my bag.
你自己先扶一下
Hold this by yourself for a second.
我找不到了 给 拿着这个
I can't find it. Here, take this.
这是什么
What is this?
一百块钱硬币
A hundred dollars in change.
婚礼要用的
We need it for the wedding.
朝新娘扔硬币是波兰的传统
It's a Polish custom to throw change at the bride.
扔硬币 活动物
Loose change? Live animals?
这是婚礼还是斗鸡赛啊
Is this a wedding or a cock fight?
麦克斯 这个好沉啊
Max, this is heavy!
你要从包包里拿什么东西呀
What do you have to get out of your bag?
-重要的东西 -是什么
- Something important. - What is it?
吃剩的肉桂卷
The rest of my Cinnabon.
麦克斯 那可是我们的竞争对手
Max, that's our competition!
我们业绩失败就是因为那破玩意
The reason for our failure is that piece of crap.
我是说...
I mean, I ca--
哇靠 真好吃
Oh, my God, this is delicious!
不 麦克斯 他要抢我们的钱袋
No! Max, he's got the money bag.
不 不许捡 不许捡
No-- No! No, no, no!
那可是我们波兰新娘的钱
That is our Polish bride money!
走开
Back off!
今天可不是招惹姐的好日子
This is not the day to screw with me.
姐的业绩垫底
I'm at the business bottom
而且从2011年后 姐穷得什么都不怕了
and I've had nothing to lose since 2011.
皇后[变装]广场站到了
Queen's Plaza.
是啊 之后就是给我儿子变装了
Yup. That's what would happen next.
她们怎么这么久不出来
What's the hold up back there?
人们都在下注打赌 说我带着妓女
People are placing bets that I'm halfway to Reno
和婚礼的礼金在去往里诺的路上了
with a hooker and the wedding cash.
别紧张 经过地铁大战后
Relax. After that subway,
麦克斯和卡洛琳需要点时间梳洗打扮
Max and Caroline needed some time to freshen up.
她们来时身上一股咱们餐厅
They came smelling like that diner cheese
我说还"没坏"的起司味道
I tell you all is still good.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
我们就像苏菲的翻版 真是松了一口气
We look just like Sophie! I am so relieved.
我还以为会穿着太夸张 没想到只是奶太小
I thought I'd be way overdressed but I'm just under-boobed.
是啊 我们赶时间
Yeah, we were in a hurry
不然我可以借她一个罩杯
or I would have loaned her a cup of mine.
好的
All right.
奥列格 不许那样打量我们
Oleg, stop looking at us like that.
没关系 你们都要嫁给我了
It's okay. I'm marrying you.
你们看起来像四顶尖合唱团
You guys look like the Four Tops.
两个顶 一个腚
Well, two tops and a bottom.
奥列格 苏菲不想让你提前看见她
Oleg, Sophie doesn't want you to see her.
骑上栗宝走红毯吧
Jump on Chestnut and start down the aisle.
栗宝 对不起 宝贝
And Chestnut, I'm sorry, baby.
我知道你不喜欢男扮女 玩变装
I know you never wanted to do drag.
阿憨 你拿着这个
And, Han, you're supposed to take this
以防红毯上发生什么"屎"
in case something happens in the aisle.
我一下从伴郎沦落成铲屎郎了
This just went from best man to worst job.
你们觉得怎么样 姑娘们
What do you think, girls?
我看起来像纯洁的处女吗
Do I look like a virgin?
听 大号声响起 我该入场了
Oh, listen! I heard the tuba. That's my cue!
进去 姑娘们 快去
Go, girls. Go!
天啊
Oh, God!
她的婚纱差点害死咱俩
Her dress almost killed us
现在直接把厄尔害死了
and now it killed Earl.
多谢大侠
Thanks.
我以为要驾白鹤归西了呢
I thought I was a goner.
下面交换誓言
Time for the vows.
上皇冠
Bring the crowns!
戴上皇冠 戴上荣耀
And crowned is married...
结为夫妻
with honor.
把皇冠举到他们头上
Raise the crowns to their heads.
快开始吧
Better go.
没有梯子 最多只能这样了
This is as good as it's gonna get without a ladder.
我 苏菲·科臣斯基
I, Sophie Kachinsky...
愿意嫁给奥列格·高里彻斯基
take you, Oleg Golishevsky
从今以后 相爱相惜
to love and to cherish,
相互拥有扶持
to have and to hold,
永远不离开你
never to leave your side
至死不渝
'til death comes to take me.
我 奥列格·高里彻斯基
I, Oleg Golishevsky,
愿意娶苏菲·科臣斯基
take you, Sophie Kachinsky,
从今以后 相爱相惜
to love and to cherish,
相互拥有扶持
to have and to hold,
永远不离开你
never to leave your side
至死不渝
'til death comes to take me.
我现在宣布你们正式结为夫妻
I pronounce you husband and wife!
麦克斯 你可以扔硬币了
Max, now you throw the coins.
说来话长
Long story.
妹子 你手速好快啊
Wow, girl, your fingers work fast.
常年解501排扣牛仔裤的纽扣练出来的
Must be from years of opening those 501 button-fly jeans...
不光自己的 还有别人的
Mine and others'.
麦克斯 我受够等待了
Max, I'm done waiting.
马上给我来一块蛋糕
I need that piece of cake right now.
我们刚才在空中九死一生
We just had a close call in the air.
离死特近 近到我们可以对
So close, we gave the finger to the pilot
隔壁飞机的飞行员竖中指
in the plane next to us.
我们差点坠机
We almost crashed,
我不想一边往下掉一边嚷
and I didn't wanna go down screaming,
"我好后悔没开托儿所"
"I should have opened a daycare center!"
我一般"往下"时都爱嚷
I usually go down screaming,
"你还没请老娘吃饭呢"
"You didn't buy me dinner!"
波妮 面对现实吧
Bonnie, let's admit it.
我们永远不会去实现我们的梦想
We're never gonna go for our dream,
就像我们永远不会去做大肠水疗
just like we never went to get those colonics.
如果我们真的想自己创业
If we really wanted our own business,
肯定一早就干了
we would have done it already,
就像麦克斯和卡洛琳
like Max and Caroline did.
你说得对 我们做到了
You're right, we did.
强哥 帮我切两块最大的
John, cut these two the biggest piece
椰子夏威夷果仁蛋糕给她俩
of coconut macadamia nut cake we have.
天啊 我觉得我高潮了
Oh my god. I think I just climaxed.
那快穿上你的内裤
Well, then pull your panties on
像平时那样赶紧溜
and slink the hell out like you usually do.
卡洛琳 我有话要跟你说
Caroline, I need to talk to you.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
工作啊 我烦恼死了
Working! I'm worry sick.
波妮和洛妮刚在外面让我想起一件事
Bonnie and Ronnie out there just reminded me of something.
除了两个阿姨在度假时喝醉之外
I mean, besides two aunts drunk on vacation.
我们都忘了我们有自己的事业
We have our own business.
嗨翻天不是我们的失败门店
The High isn't our failure.
我们已经有一个自己的失败门店
We already have our very own failure
就是麦克斯自制小蛋糕店啊
called Max's Homemade Cupcakes.
如果我们留在这工作
And if we stay here, we're building
那就是帮别人筑梦 荒废自己的梦
someone else's dream, not ours.
还有如果留在这
Also, if we stay,
你的屁股会胖得像一座房子那么大
your ass will be the size of a house.
你在这最近一次觉得开心是什么时候
I mean, when was the last time you felt happy here?
30秒之前 你冲进来说
Like 30 seconds ago when you said this place
这不是我们的失败门店 于是我想起
wasn't our failure and I remembered I was holding
我另一只手还有一个可以吃
another one of these in my other hand.
咱们离开机场吧
Let's get out of this airport.
再也不用天天看到白痴机场热门小说了
We never have to see another Nicholas Sparks novel again.
首先我们得处理掉
First, we have to get rid
那两张去巴黎的飞机票
of those two plane tickets to Paris.
有必要吗
Do we?
如果我们注定失败
I mean, if we're gonna fail
那去巴黎先玩一周 回来再失败也无妨
we can still do that after a week in Paris, right?
对
Right.
我太兴奋了 我从来没坐过头等舱
I'm so stoked! I've never been in first class.
不过麦克斯 这是经济舱
Except, Max, this is coach.
我退了一张头等舱机票 拿另外一张
I got a refund on one ticket and traded in the other
换了两张经济舱机票 订了一家便宜的酒店
to buy two coach tickets and to pay for a cheap hotel.
我太兴奋了 我从来没坐过经济舱
I'm so stoked. I've never been in coach.
对了 还留了点钱在巴黎花
And also so we have money to spend.
我们应该可以在巴黎用12美元过一周吧
We should be able to do Paris for a week on $12.
当然可以啦
Of course, we can.
话说头等舱和经济舱到底区别在哪里
What's the difference between coach and first, anyway?
在香槟
The champagne.
稍后会给你们上好吃的饼干[笑话]
We'll be back with the good crackers,
我不是说我们哟
and I don't mean us.
亲爱的 在经历完今年这么多事以后
Well, partner, after all we've been through this year,
无论接下来会发生什么事
whatever comes next,
我感觉都做好迎接的准备了
I kinda feel ready for it.
机组人员 飞机即将起飞
Flight crew, prepare for take-off.
现在换你在哼歌了
Hey, now you're humming.
是吗
I am?
我可以拿香槟换啤酒吗
Hey, can I trade this in for a beer?